[EPIC]⚡ I hate California. I'm gonna go get me in the car.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 with culture and like, we need a little bit of race or a seat. I'm not a bit of a seat.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I'm just going to go to the bany boy. Just go to the bany boy.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I think she's got a pretty common demand in jail.
[EPIC]⚡ .
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Pull yourself up, daddy.
[EPIC]⚡ and I was...
[EPIC]⚡ That's amazing. Back.
[EPIC]⚡ She is a big heart.
[EPIC]⚡ which is also.
[EPIC]⚡ So
[EPIC]⚡ I'm not.
[EPIC]⚡ have the college.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ a little bit.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I'm not tired.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Alright. Got it.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ I don't need to do that. I wanted it to be special. Why?
[EPIC]⚡ So, I'm going to smash the thanks to you, man. We're afraid.
[EPIC]⚡ It's never enough. It is enough. For a frayed of what the future will frayed. We're afraid.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 Mom? No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You want to relax? No, you want to come on and say that I'm totally patient. What the heck? You're so glad to see. You've lost the fear.
[DIALOGUE]🗣 I want to move.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ very
[EPIC]⚡ Would you be me?
[DIALOGUE]🗣 This is the best version.
[EPIC]⚡ Thank you.
[EPIC]⚡ Yeah.
[HAPPY]😊 Yeah.